JOHN MUSUSA | FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Mobile: 073 314 3667

Whatsapp: 068 568 0276

Email: djjakezofficial85@gmail.com



My name is John Mususa I'm an enthusiastic hard working person. I specialize in Web Development with a handful set of skills. I have great communication skills both spoken and written as one believes the key to success is Team Work and Communication. I'm a quick learner suitable for any role fast and adaptive with an analytical approach to solving problems. I have a passion for learning, developing always positive strive for nothing but success.

Core Qualification Skills

- Good IT Skills(Specialize in coding Web Design)
- Fantastic Computer Skills
- Customer Services + Retail Skills
- Work is presented at it's best done accurate on Time
- Leadership Skills Ability to work well under pressure
- Currently studying Digital Marking(SEO) with Graphic Design
- Frontend Web Developer
- Sketch and Design (Artist)

Experiences

2020-2022

Web Developer Internship

- Web Development | Web Designing Concepts of Frontend Web Dev and much more.
- HTML|CSS|JAVASCRIPT|BOOTSTRAP
- Designing and coding learning the aspects of Web Development
- 2020-2023 Freelance Web Developer
- Currently a freelance Web Developer with experience as Frontend Web Developer have worked on couple of Projects and Designs that's available for display on request

Additional Work Experience

McDonalds Sun Valley Long Beach Mall

I have worked by McDonalds located at Sun Valley Mall with good environmental work experience as an All Runner doing a little bit of everything such as:

- Cashier | Retail Skills | Great Kitchen Skills
- Grill Kitchen Skill
- Food assembly and attention to details
- Customer Service | Till Management
- Greeting and Serving Customers
- Assisting at any Area doing a bit of everything

References: Store Manager - Thelma Brown (061 601 8819)

Education

2015-2019

- Matriculated Grade 12 (Ocean View High School)
- Top Achiever for Computer Application Technology (Grade 11)

2018-2019

- Certificate of Attendance at the Metropolition Police Youth Leadership Camp (at Princess Vi Eco Center)
- Leadership Skills the ability to work under pressure well and deliver good work results.

2020-2022

- Graduated College (Cape Audio College)
- Professional DJ | Musician Artist | Pioneer DJ Academy

Skills

- Frontend Web Developer
- HTML|CSS|JAVASCRIPT|BOOTSTRAP
- SKETCH AND DESIGN (ART)
- MUSIC PRODUCTION
- PROFESSIONAL DJ ENTERTAINMENT
- COMPUTER SKILLS
- PHOTOSHOP | CANVA | FIGMA (learning to master all aspects)
- CUSTOMER SERVICES
- LEADERSHIP SKILLS
- PHOTOSHOP|CANVA|FIGMA
- GOOD COMMUNICATION SKILLS
- GRILL & KITCHEN SKILLS ATTENTION TO DETAIL
- WORK IS PRESENTED AT ITS BEST DONR ACCURATE ON TIME
- THE ABILITY TO MULTITASK AND HANDLE DIFFERENT TASKS PRESENTED

Languages: English and Afrikaans

<u>References:</u> Avaliable on request